<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<travelSightbase xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="travelSight.xsd">
    <about>
        <title>M &amp; T Travel Factory</title>
        <author>Meg Wang</author>
        <description>
            <p>Why we travel</p>
                <p>For us, travelling is one of our favorite hobbies. It is a time to relax and enjoy our stay in a environment different to what we have back at home. Travelling allows us to meet new people, new adventures, new food and new experiences. We travel to see what the world is like beyond our living room, classrooms and reading rooms.</p>                
                <p>We travel so we can lose ourselves in a world that we are trying to understand and find ourselves at the same time. Through travelling, we learn to open our eyes and immerse ourselves in a world that we have only seen through pictures and movies. We spend our money travelling but get richer in the process.</p>
            <p>By T</p>
            <ul>
                <li>NO.1 Maldives</li>
                <li>NO.2 Paris</li>
                <li>NO.3 Venice</li>
                <li>NO.4 Helsinki</li>
                <li>NO.5 Taiwan</li>
                <li>NO.6 Greece</li>
                <li>NO.7 Sydney</li>
                <li>NO.8 Cuba</li>
                <li>NO.9 Barcelona</li>
                <li>NO.10 London</li>
                <li>NO.11 Maui</li>
                <li>NO.12 Prague</li>
                <li>NO.13 Vancouver</li>
                <li>NO.14 Budapest</li>
                <li>NO.15 Hong Kong</li>
            </ul>
        </description>
    </about>

    <sourceDefs>
        <sourceDef id="s01">
            <title>visitMaldives</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>http://www.visitmaldives.com/en</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s02">
            <title>gogobot</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.gogobot.com</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s03">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/france</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s04">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/helsinki</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s05">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s06">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/greece</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s07">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/australia</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s08">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/cuba</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s09">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/barcelona</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s10">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/london</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s11">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s12">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/prague</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s13">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/vancouver</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s14">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/budapest</url>
        </sourceDef>
        <sourceDef id="s15">
            <title>Lonely Planet</title>
            <description>
                <p>official website</p>
            </description>
            <url>www.lonelyplanet.com/hongkong</url>
        </sourceDef>
    </sourceDefs>

    <travelSights>
        <travelSight id="site1" rank="1" tag="natural sight, diving, fishing, beach">
            <title>Maldives</title>
            <description>                
                <p><b>Welcome to the <u>Maldives!</u></b></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Where <i>sands</i> are white as the smiles of the locals</li>
                    <li>Where <i>fish</i> swim happily in the warm waters of the Indian Ocean</li>
                    <li>Where the <i>weather</i> is a dream, and the deep rays of the sun waits to engulf
                        you in their arms</li>
                </ul>
                <p>For more information, please look into <pubMentioned>"Lonely Planet"</pubMentioned> 
                    <xref id="x01" type="web" dest="http://www.lonelyplanet.com/search?q=maldives">
                    <xrefText> (<hotText>http://www.lonelyplanet.com/search?q=maldives</hotText>) </xrefText>
                </xref>
                </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s01</sourceRefId>
                <sourceRefId>s02</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="Republic of Maldives"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="maldives1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>
            <review id="r1">
                <p><b>Jelly</b>: What an amazing place. Be sure to be at the summit before the
                    sunrise. It's like seeing a sci-fi movie come to life. Recommended for: Outdoor
                    Enthusiasts</p>
            </review>
            <review id="r16">
                <p><b>Young</b>: Must see sunrise place. Worth the time to go there, be ready for
                    the cold though. Pack up some warm clothes. Recommended for: Backpackers History
                    Buffs Adventure Travelers</p>
            </review>
            <highLight>
                <p>The Maldives is the perfect destination for the most ardent of divers or for the
                    first time snorkeller with a huge range of marine biodiversity and exceptional
                    visibility </p>
             </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p>You won't find a single echoey corridor anywhere in the Maldives</p>
            </highLight>


            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Outdoor Sports</title>
                    <telephone>206-777-7777</telephone>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Fish Market</title>
                    <address>Boduthankurufaanu Magu, Malé, Maldives </address>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>National Museum</title>
                    <address>Chandhanee Magu, Malé, Maldives</address>
                    <openHours>10am-5pm Sun-Thu</openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site5</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site8</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site11</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>

        <travelSight id="site2" rank="2" tag="Romantic, Historical, Literatural">
            <title>Paris</title>
            <description>
                <p> France seduces travellers with its unfalteringly familiar culture, woven around
                    cafe terraces, village-square markets and lace-curtained bistros with their plat
                    du jour chalked on the board. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s03</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="France"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="paris1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>

            <review id="r2">
                <p> France has been home for two decades yet I can’t shake off that uncanny feeling
                    I’m on holiday – French art de vivre (art of living) is just too good and I’m
                    mad about it. From my Haute-Savoie house on Lake Geneva’s southern shore, the
                    dark green hills of the Jura and un café in the wisteria-draped village bar are
                    my wake-up call. Weekends of endless possibilities punctuate the gentle rhythm
                    of village life: ravishing art museums in Lyon and Paris, hiking and skiing in
                    the Alps, paddle boarding on the glittering lake, road trips to Beaujolais and
                    Burgundy and other regions so different they could be another country. France’s
                    sheer variety never ceases to amaze me. </p>
            </review>


            <highLight>
                <p> Outdoor Action </p>
                <p> And then there is the terroir (land) and the varied journey it weaves from
                    northern France's cliffs and sand dunes to the piercing blue sea of the French
                    Riviera and Corsica's green oak forests. Outdoor action is what France's lyrical
                    landscape demands – and there's something for everybody. Whether you end up
                    walking barefoot across wave-rippled sand to Mont St-Michel, riding a cable car
                    to glacial panoramas above Chamonix, or cartwheeling down Europe's highest sand
                    dune, France does not disappoint. Its great outdoors is thrilling, with endless
                    opportunities and the next adventure begging to be had. Allez! </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Art de Vivre </p>
                <p> The rhythm of daily life – dictated by the seasons in the depths of la France
                    profonde (rural France) – exudes an intimacy that gets under your skin. Don’t
                    resist. Rather, live the French lifestyle. Embrace the luxury of simple,
                    everyday rituals being transformed into unforgettable moments, be it a coffee
                    and croissant in the Parisian cafe where Sartre and Simone de Beauvoir met to
                    philosophise, a stroll through the lily-clad gardens Monet painted, or a walk on
                    a beach in Brittany scented with the subtle infusion of language, music and
                    mythology brought by 5th-century Celtic invaders. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Gastronomy </p>
                <p> Food is of enormous importance to the French, and each region has its own
                    specialities alongside French classics. The daily culinary agenda takes no
                    prisoners: breakfasting on warm croissants from the boulangerie, stopping off at
                    Parisian bistros, and shopping at the market are all second nature to the French
                    – and it really would rude to refuse. But French gastronomy goes far deeper than
                    just eating exceedingly well. Its experiential nature means there is always
                    something tasty to observe, learn and try, wherever you are – be it flipping
                    crepes in Brittany or chinking Champagne flutes in ancient Reims cellars, the
                    culinary opportunities are endless. </p>
            </highLight>

            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Eiffel Towl</title>
                    <telephone> +33 892701239 </telephone>
                    <address> Champ de Mars, 5 av Anatole France, 7e </address>
                    <gettingThere> Metro: Bir Hakeim Train: Champ de Mars-Tour Eiffel </gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo> www.tour-eiffel.fr </moreInfo>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title> Cathedrale Notre Dame </title>
                    <telephone/>
                    <address> Place Notre Dame,Amiens,France </address>
                    <gettingThere/>
                    <openHours> cathedral 8.30am-6.15pm daily, north tower afternoon only Wed-Mon
                    </openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site9</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site12</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site14</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>

        <travelSight id="site3" rank="3" tag="Historical; Lifestype ">
            <title>Venice</title>
            <description>
                <p> Imagine the audacity of building a city of marble palaces on a lagoon – and that
                    was only the start. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s04</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="Italy"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="venice1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>

            <review id="r3">
                <p> Why I Love Venice </p>
                <p> <p>By Cristian Bonetto, Writer: </p>Venice is the consummate magician. It makes marble
                    palaces vanish into silent fogs, labyrinthine calli (streets) disappear at the
                    whim of moody tides, and can even turn the most pedestrian of people into
                    fantastical, masked creatures. Just like its world-famous Carnevale, Venice
                    thrives on mystery and awe, from the secret passageways that riddle Gothic
                    Palazzo Ducale, to the esoteric powers of the Basilica di Santa Maria della
                    Salute, to the inexplicable radiance of Titian's Assunta altarpiece. After
                    countless sojourns, I am yet to tire of the place. Some spells are simply too
                    hard to break. </p>
            </review>


            <highLight>
                <p> Venetian Feasts </p>
                <p> Garden islands and lagoon aquaculture yield speciality produce and seafood you
                    won’t find elsewhere – all highlighted in inventive Venetian cuisine, with
                    tantalising traces of ancient spice routes. The city knows how to put on a royal
                    spread, as France’s King Henry III once found out when faced with 1200 dishes
                    and 200 bonbons. Today such feasts are available in miniature at happy hour,
                    when bars mount lavish spreads of cicheti (Venetian tapas). Save room and time
                    for a proper sit-down Venetian meal, with lagoon seafood to match views at
                    canalside bistros and toasts with Veneto’s signature bubbly, prosecco. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Historic Firsts </p>
                <p> The city built on water was never afraid to attempt the impossible. When plague
                    struck, Venice consulted its brain trust of Mediterranean doctors, who
                    recommended a precaution that has saved untold lives since: quarantine. Under
                    attack by Genovese rivals, Venice’s Arsenale shipyards innovated the assembly
                    line, producing a new warship every day to defeat Genoa. After Genoa backed
                    Christopher Columbus' venture to the New World, Venice's shipping fortunes began
                    to fade – but Venice wasn't about to relinquish the world stage, going on to
                    become the launching pad for baroque music and modern opera. </p>
            </highLight>

            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title> Palazzo Ducale </title>
                    <address> Piazzetta San Marco 52, Venice, Italy </address>
                    <gettingThere> Ferry:San Zaccaria </gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo>www.palazzoducale.visitmuve.it</moreInfo>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site6</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site9</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site12</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>

        <travelSight id="site4" rank="4" tag="Natural; Greens; Snow; Wildlife">
            <title>Helsinki</title>
            <description>
                <p> It’s fitting that harbourside Helsinki, capital of a country with such watery
                    geography, melds so graciously into the Baltic. Half the city seems liquid, and
                    the writhings of the complex coastline include any number of bays, inlets and
                    islands. </p>
                <p> Though Helsinki can seem a younger sibling to other Scandinavian capitals, it’s
                    the one that went to art school, scorns pop music and works in a cutting-edge
                    studio. The design scene here is legendary, whether you're browsing showroom
                    brands or taking the backstreet hipster trail. The city's gourmet side is also
                    flourishing, with new gastro eateries offering locally sourced tasting menus
                    popping up at dizzying speed. </p>
                <p> Nevertheless, much of what is lovable in Helsinki is older. Its understated yet
                    glorious art-nouveau buildings, the spacious elegance of its centenarian cafes,
                    dozens of museums carefully preserving Finnish heritage, restaurants that have
                    changed neither menu nor furnishings since the 1930s: all part of the city’s
                    quirky charm. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s05</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="Finland"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="finland1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>

            <review id="r4">
                <p> By Andy Symington, Writer: </p>
                <p> My first impression of Finland was a winter one, when snow-hushed forests and
                    Christmastime conviviality made an instant impact. You must come back in summer,
                    everyone said, so I did, for midnight daytime saunas by impossibly picturesque
                    lakes and melt-in-the-mouth fresh berries and potatoes. Fresh air, the Lapland
                    wilderness, the hiking, the wildlife: it's a natural wonderland within an
                    impressively technological modern nation. The real bonus? The Finns, who do
                    their own thing and are much the better for it. Independent, loyal and welcoming
                    – memorable people in an inspirational country. Make it your business to get to
                    know some. </p>
            </review>


            <highLight>
                <p> City Lights </p>
                <p> Don’t get the idea that the country’s just a backwoods emptiness, though.
                    Vibrant cities stock the southern parts, headed by the capital, Helsinki, a
                    cutting-edge urban space with world-famous design and music scenes. Embraced by
                    the Baltic, it’s an enticing ensemble of modern and stately architecture, island
                    restaurants, and stylish and quirky bars. And complaints about Finnish food are
                    so last century: the ‘new Suomi’ restaurant scene is kicking, with locally
                    foraged flavours to the fore. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Call of the Wild </p>
                <p> The Finland you encounter will depend on the season of your visit, but whatever
                    the month, the call of the wilderness is a siren song not to be resisted.
                    There’s something pure in the Finnish air and spirit that’s really vital and
                    exciting; it’s an invitation to get out and active year-round. With vast tracts
                    of forest, speckled by picture-perfect lakes as if an artist had flicked a blue
                    paintbrush at the map, Suomi offers some of Europe’s best hiking, kayaking and
                    canoeing. A fabulous network of national parks has well-marked routes and
                    regularly spaced huts for overnighting. Bears and elk deep in the forests can be
                    observed on nature-watching trips. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Summer Days </p>
                <p> Finland’s short but reliable sunny season sees the country burst into life.
                    Finns seem to want to suck every last golden drop out of the summer in the hope
                    that it will last them through the long dark winter months, and there’s an
                    explosion of good cheer and optimism. It’s a time for music festivals, art
                    exhibitions, lake cruises, midnight sunshine on convivial beer terraces, lazy
                    days at remote waterside cottages and mouth-watering market produce. </p>
            </highLight>

            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Temppeliaukion Kirkko</title>
                    <address> Lutherinkato 3, Helsinki, Finland </address>
                    <moreInfo>www.helsinginseurakunnat.fi</moreInfo>
                    <openHours> 10am-5.45pm Mon-Sat, 11.45am-5.45pm Sun Jun-Aug, to 5pm Sep-May
                    </openHours>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title> Ateneum </title>
                    <address> Kaivokatu 2 </address>
                    <openHours> 10am-6pm Tue, Fri, 9am-8pm Wed,Thu, 10am-5pm Sat,Sun </openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site8</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site9</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>

        <travelSight id="site5" rank="5" tag="Food, Nature, Life, Adventure, Tradition">
            <title>Taiwan</title>
            <description>
                <p> With its all-around adventure landscape, heritage-rich capital, diverse folk
                    traditions and feted night market scene, Taiwan offers a continent-sized travel
                    list for one green island. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s06</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="China"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="taiwan1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>

            <review id="r5">
                <p> By Robert Kelly, Writer: </p>
                <p> I have been living in Taiwan for the past 17 years and when I wake up in the
                    morning I still wonder how I can possibly find time for all the new passions
                    I've developed here: go cycle or hike in the lush mountains in my Taipei
                    neighbourhood? Visit a traditional temple and study historical allusions in yet
                    another sculptured masterpiece? Try a new strain of organic tea or single-origin
                    coffee? Improve my Mandarin? Or just catch the latest mass rally downtown of
                    locals trying to make this a better place? I love that Taiwan gives me the
                    freedom to go anywhere, do anything, and that no matter what I delve into, I'm
                    always rewarded for going deeper. </p>
            </review>


            <highLight>
                <p> Asian Values On Their Terms </p>
                <p> Defying those who said it wasn't in their DNA, the Taiwanese have created Asia's
                    most vibrant democracy, and liberal society, with a raucous free press, gender
                    equality and respect for human rights and increasingly animal rights as well.
                    The ancestors are still worshipped, and mum and dad still get their dues, but
                    woe befall the politician who thinks it's the people who must pander, and not
                    him. If you want to catch a glimpse of the people's passion for protest, check
                    out Taipei Main Station on most weekends, or just follow the local news. </p>
            </highLight>

            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Miaokou Night Market</title>
                    <address>Keelung Taiwan</address>
                    <openHours>hours vary</openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site15</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>
        <travelSight id="site6" rank="6" tag="Socially Spirited; Natural; Cultural; Lifestyle">
            <title>Greece</title>
            <description>
                <p> Socially Spirited </p>
                <p> Greeks are truly social beings. Their families are extended and they are quick
                    to welcome in newcomers, whether for a coffee, a shot of ouzo, a chorus on the
                    bouzouki or a heated debate. Greeks are passionate, if nothing else, and this
                    passion continues to drive society forward despite the current economic turmoil.
                    Life is lived to the fullest, even at the most difficult of times, and herein
                    lies the secret of how a country, seemingly riddled with challenges, is full of
                    people who remain so in love with life. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s01</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="Greece"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="greece1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>

            <review id="r6">
                <p> By Korina Miller, Writer: </p>
                <p> I first visited Greece as an 18-year-old, sleeping on the decks of slow-moving
                    ferries, living on olives and feta, and constantly salt-crusted from swimming in
                    the deep blue Aegean. But it was a starlit performance at the 3rd-century BC
                    Theatre of Epidavros that sealed my love of the country. Watching the ancient
                    Greek drama unfold before me as I sat on stone seats worn smooth by thousands of
                    years of use, I felt caught in a moment that seemed to sidestep time. I love
                    Greece because magical moments like that one aren’t so hard to find here. </p>
            </review>


            <highLight>
                <p> Naturally Inviting </p>
                <p> It’s easy to understand how so many myths of gods and giants originated in this
                    vast and varied landscape, with wide open skies and a sea speckled with islands,
                    where days melt from one to the next while you relish the white-sand and
                    palm-fringed beaches. Greece is a magnet for anyone who enjoys the great
                    outdoors. Wander along cobbled, Byzantine footpaths, hike into volcanoes, watch
                    for dolphins and sea turtles, and cycle through lush forests. Discover
                    world-class kitesurfing, diving and rock-climbing locations or simply hop on a
                    boat and set sail into the glittering blue beyond. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Sumptuous Feasting </p>
                <p> Greeks pride themselves on their cuisine and will go out of their way to ensure
                    you are well fed. The tang of homemade tzatziki and the aroma of souvlaki
                    grilling are just the beginning. Taste test your way through regional cheeses –
                    from crumbling feta to honeyed soft cheeses and sharp, hard rounds. Dig into
                    rich layers of mousakas and sip crisp wine from grapes ripened under the hot
                    Mediterranean sun. The Italian legacy of pasta is paired with Greek specialties
                    like lobster, while Turkish spices find their way into delicate sweets. Mussels
                    are steamed in ouzo, bread is baked with olives and fish is cooked straight from
                    the sea. </p>
            </highLight>

            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Acropolis</title>
                    <telephone> +30 2103210219 </telephone>
                    <address> Athens, Greece </address>
                    <gettingThere> Metro: Akropoli </gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo> http://odysseus.culture.gr </moreInfo>
                    <openHours> 8am-8pm Apr-Oct, to 5pm Nov-Mar, last entry 30min before closing
                    </openHours>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Meteora</title>
                    <telephone> +30 2432022649 </telephone>
                    <address> cnr Kastraki &amp; Kalambaka overlooking the valley of Pinios </address>
                    <moreInfo> www.gnto.gr </moreInfo>
                    <openHours> 09:00-13:00 &amp; 15:00-17:00 </openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site8</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site11</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>

        <travelSight id="site7" rank="7" tag="Nature, Adventure, Family">
            <title>Sydney</title>
            <description>
                <p> Is the grass always greener on the other side of the fence? Peek over the
                    pickets and find out. This vast country is affluent, multicultural and laced
                    with natural splendour. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s07</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="Australia"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="sydney1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>

            <review id="r7">
                <p> By Charles Rawlings-Way, Meg Worby, Writers: </p>
                <p> I've been living in this great southern land for 30-something years, and there
                    are still places I haven't explored. Australia is just so damn big. Even if we
                    spent the next 30-something years on an endless round-Australia road trip,
                    there'd still be surprises out there. And that, for a restless road-addict, is a
                    very comforting reality. </p>
            </review>


            <highLight>
                <p> Hip Cities </p>
                <p> Most Australians live along the coast, and most of these folks live in cities –
                    89% of Australians, in fact. It follows that cities here are a lot of fun.
                    Sydney is a glamorous collusion of beaches, boutiques and bars. Melbourne is all
                    arts, alleyways and Aussie Rules football. Brisbane is a subtropical town on the
                    way up; Adelaide has festive grace and pubby poise. Boomtown Perth breathes West
                    Coast optimism; Canberra transcends political agendas. While the tropical
                    northern frontier town of Darwin, and the chilly southern sandstone city of
                    Hobart, couldn't be more different. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> It's a Wide Open Road </p>
                <p> There's a heckuva lot of tarmac across this wide brown land. From Margaret River
                    to Cooktown, Jabiru to Dover, the best way to appreciate Australia is to hit the
                    road. Car hire is relatively affordable, road conditions are generally good, and
                    beyond the big cities traffic fades away. If you're driving a campervan, you'll
                    find well-appointed caravan parks in most sizable towns. If you're feeling
                    adventurous, hire a 4WD and go off-road: Australia's national parks and secluded
                    corners are custom-made for camping trips down the dirt road. </p>
            </highLight>

            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title> Sydney Opera House </title>
                    <telephone> +61 292507250 </telephone>
                    <address> Bennelong point, Sydney, Australia </address>
                    <gettingThere> Train: Circular Quay </gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo> www.sydneyoperahouse.com </moreInfo>
                    <openHours> tours 9am-5pm </openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site11</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site13</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>

        <travelSight id="site8" rank="8" tag="Natural; Historical Heritage; Beaches">
            <title>Cuba</title>
            <description>
                <p> Timeworn but magnificent, dilapidated but dignified, fun yet maddeningly
                    frustrating - Cuba is a country of indefinable magic. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s08</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="Cuba"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="cuba1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>

            <review id="r8">
                <p> By Brendan Sainsbury, Writer: </p>
                <p> When I think of Cuba, I always think of my first night back in Havana after a
                    break; the busy atmospheric streets, the snapshots of lives lived out in the
                    open, and the unmistakable aromas: tropical papaya mixed with tobacco leaf,
                    petrol and musty carpets. Cuba is a forbidden fruit, a complex country of
                    head-scratching contradictions, which, however many times you visit, will never
                    adequately answer all your questions. Most of all I love Cuba's musicality,
                    robust culture, wonderfully preserved history, and the fact that it can
                    frustrate you one minute and unexpectedly inspire you the next. </p>
            </review>


            <highLight>
                <p> Beyond the Beaches </p>
                <p> Although the attractive arcs of white sand that pepper its north coast are
                    sublime, explore beyond Cuba's beaches and you’re in a different domain, a land
                    of fecund forests and crocodile-infested swamps, suburbia-free countryside and
                    rugged mountains as famous for their revolutionary folklore as for their endemic
                    species. Cuba, once observed German scientist Alexander von Humboldt, is a kind
                    of Caribbean Galapagos where contradictory curiosities coexist. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Historical Heritage </p>
                <p> Meticulously preserved, Cuba’s colonial cities haven’t changed much since
                    musket-toting pirates stalked the Caribbean. The atmosphere and architecture is
                    particularly stirring in the Unesco-listed cities – Havana, Trinidad, Cienfuegos
                    and Camagüey – where grandiose squares and cobbled streets tell erstwhile tales
                    of opulence and intrigue. Elsewhere many buildings lie ruined and tattered like
                    aging dowagers waiting for a facelift. With more funds, these heirlooms may yet
                    emulate the colonial treasures in Havana and Trinidad, further proof that the
                    safeguarding of Cuba’s historical legacy has been one of the revolution’s
                    greatest achievements. | </p>
            </highLight>
            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Malecon</title>
                    <address> Havana, Cuba </address>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Zoologico de Piedras</title>
                    <address>Guantanamo, Cuba</address>
                    <openHours>9am-6am Mon-Sat</openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site1</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site6</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>
        <travelSight id="site9" rank="9" tag="Iberian Sun; Architecture;">
            <title>Barcelona</title>
            <description>
                <p> Barcelona is an enchanting seaside city with boundless culture, fabled
                    architecture, and a world-class drinking and dining scene. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s09</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="Spain"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="barcelona1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>
            <review id="r9">
                <p> By Regis St Louis, Writer: </p>
                <p> I love the sea, and taking an early-morning jog along the Mediterranean is my
                    favourite way to start the day. I'm also a bit of a history nerd, and relish
                    strolling the cobblestone lanes of the Gothic quarter, thinking about all the
                    people in past centuries who walked these same streets. And then there's the
                    food and drink – the first-rate tapas bars, the abundant and inexpensive wine,
                    the superb and reasonably priced multicourse lunches. Add to all this Catalan
                    creativity (Modernisme, Miró, Dalí), bohemian bars and stunning nearby getaways
                    and you have, quite simply, one of the world's most captivating cities. | </p>
            </review>
            <highLight>
                <p> Architecture of the Ages </p>
                <p> Barcelona's architectural treasures span 2000-plus years. Towering temple
                    columns, ancient city walls and subterranean stone corridors provide a window
                    into Roman-era Barcino. Fast forward a thousand years to the Middle Ages by
                    taking a stroll through the shadowy lanes of the Gothic quarter, past tranquil
                    plazas and soaring 14th-century cathedrals. In other parts of town bloom the
                    sculptural masterpieces of Modernisme, a mix of ingenious and whimsical
                    creations by Gaudí and his Catalan architectural contemporaries, for which this
                    city is so well known. Barcelona has also long inspired artists, including the
                    likes of Salvador Dalí, Pablo Picasso and Joan Miró, whose works are in bold
                    display in the city's myriad museums. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Under the Iberian Sun </p>
                <p> The deep blue Mediterranean beckons. Sun-drenched beaches make a fine backdrop
                    to a jog, bike ride or long leisurely stroll along the seaside – followed by a
                    refreshing dip, of course. You can also enjoy the view from out on the water
                    while kayaking, stand-up paddleboarding or taking it easy on a sunset cruise.
                    Looming behind the city, the rolling forest-covered Collserola Hills provide a
                    scenic setting for hiking, mountain biking or just admiring the view. Closer to
                    the city centre, hilltop Montjuïc offers endless exploring amid botanic and
                    sculpture gardens, an old castle and first-rate museums with panoramic views at
                    every turn </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> A Moveable Feast </p>
                <p> Barcelona's great artistic traditions don't end at the canvas. The masters of
                    molecular gastronomy – Albert Adrià, Carles Abellan et al – are part of the long
                    and celebrated tradition of Catalan cooking. Simple, flavourful ingredients –
                    seafood, jamón (cured ham), market-fresh produce – are transformed into
                    remarkable delicacies and then served up in captivating settings. You can feast
                    on hearty, rich paella at an outdoor table overlooking the sea or step back to
                    the 1920s at an elegant art nouveau–filled dining room. Barcelona's wide-ranging
                    palate adds further complexity: Basque-style tapas bars, Galician seafood
                    taverns, avant-garde Japanese restaurants and sinful chocolate shops are all
                    essential parts of the culinary landscape. </p>
            </highLight>
            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>La Rambla</title>
                    <address> Barcelona, Spain </address>
                    <gettingThere> Metro: Catalunya, Liceu, Drassanes </gettingThere>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>La Sagrada Familia</title>
                    <telephone> +34 932073031 </telephone>
                    <address> Carrer de Mallorca 401 </address>
                    <gettingThere> Metro: Sagrada Familia </gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo> www.sagradafamilia.cat </moreInfo>
                    <openHours> 9am - 8pm Apr-Sep, to 6pm Oct - Mar </openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site2</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site12</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>
        <travelSight id="site10" rank="10" tag="Modern; Time Travel; Business; Lifestyle">
            <title>London</title>
            <description>
                <p> One of the world's most visited cities, London has something for everyone: from
                    history and culture to fine food and good times. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s10</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="UK"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="london1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>
            <review id="r10">
                <p> By Steve Fallon, Writer: </p>
                <p> Like most Londoners, I revel in all our familiar landmarks – Big Ben, Tower
                    Bridge, the murky Thames, the London Eye. I still thank the former government
                    that made some of the greatest museums and art galleries in the world free to
                    one and all. The choice of restaurants, bars and clubs is legion, and what’s not
                    to love about a city with more lush parkland than any other world capital? But
                    the one thing that sets my adopted city apart from any other is its amazing
                    tolerance. 'As long as you don’t scare the horses, mate, you’ll be all right
                    here,’ I was told when I arrived here more than 20 years ago. Guess what… It
                    still hasn’t happened. </p>
            </review>
            <highLight>
                <p> Time Travel </p>
                <p> London is immersed in history, with more than its share of mind-blowing
                    antiquity and historic splendour. London’s buildings are eye-catching milestones
                    in the city’s unique and compelling biography, and a great many of them – the
                    Tower of London, Westminster Abbey, Big Ben – are familiar landmarks. There’s
                    more than enough innovation (the Shard, the London Eye, the planned Garden
                    Bridge) to put a crackle in the air, but it never drowns out London’s
                    well-preserved, centuries-old narrative. Architectural grandeur rises up all
                    around you in the West End, ancient remains dot the City and charming pubs
                    punctuate the banks of the Thames. Take your pick. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> A Tale of Two Cities </p>
                <p> London is as much about wide-open spaces and leafy escapes as it is
                    high-density, sight-packed exploration. Central London is where you will find
                    the major museums, galleries and most iconic sights, but visit Hampstead Heath
                    or the new Queen Elizabeth Olympic Park to escape the crowds and view the city’s
                    greener hues up close. Or venture even further out to Kew Gardens, Richmond or
                    Hampton Court Palace for excellent panoramas of riverside London. </p>
            </highLight>
            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>National Gallery</title>
                    <address>Trafalfar Sq WC2</address>
                    <gettingThere>Tube: Charing Cross</gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo>www.nationalgallery.org.uk</moreInfo>
                    <openHours>10am-6am Sat-Thu, to 9pm Fri</openHours>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>British Museum</title>
                    <telephone>+44 2073238000</telephone>
                    <address>Great Russell St</address>
                    <gettingThere>Tube:britishmuseum.org</gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo>www.britishmuseum.org</moreInfo>
                    <openHours>10am-5.30pm Sat-Thu,to8:30pm Fri</openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site13</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site15</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>
        <travelSight id="site11" rank="11" tag="Natural; Adventure; Outdoor; Island">
            <title>Maui</title>
            <description>
                <p> When it comes to outdoor adventure, Maui wins best in show. Just check out that
                    zipliner launching into a canopy of green. Or the mountain biker hurtling past
                    eucalyptus and pine. Hikers have it darn good too, with trails winding through
                    lava flows and bamboo forests. Along the coast, surfers barrel through waves,
                    windboarders skim across whitecaps and snorkelers glide beside green turtles.
                </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s11</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="USA"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="maui1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>
            <review id="r11">
                <p> And we haven't even mentioned Maui's most iconic adventures – all of them
                    flanked by once-in-a-lifetime backdrops. Along the Road to Hana, lofty
                    waterfalls plunge into shimmering pools. A mesmerizing sunrise illuminates the
                    cindery summit of Haleakalā. And the view from Makena Bay? Downright sublime in
                    winter when kayakers share the sea with frolicking humpback whales. </p>
            </review>


            <highLight>
                <p> Top-notch restaurants and lodging enhance the island's natural charms. From
                    scrappy food trucks to white-linen dining rooms, eateries embrace local food and
                    its traditions. Resorts wow guests with impeccable service and prime seaside
                    locations. </p>
            </highLight>
            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Haleakala National Park</title>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>The Road to Hana</title>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Pacific Whale Foundation</title>
                    <telephone>+1 8086677447</telephone>
                    <address>612 Front St, Lahaina USA</address>
                    <moreInfo>www.pacificwhale.org</moreInfo>
                    <openHours>reservations 6am-9pm,snorkel tours from 7am</openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site1</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site8</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>
        <travelSight id="site12" rank="12" tag="Nature, Old Town, Experience, Historical">
            <title>Prague</title>
            <description>
                <p> Prague is the equal of Paris in terms of beauty. Its history goes back a
                    millennium. And the beer? The best in Europe. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s12</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="Czech Republic"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="prague1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>
            <review id="r12">
                <p> By Neil Wilson </p>
                <p> How can you not love a city that has a pub with vinyl cushions on the wall above
                    the gents' urinal, so you can rest your head while you 'go'? Where you can order
                    a beer without speaking, simply by placing a beer mat on the table? And where
                    that beer is probably the best in the world? But it's not just exquisite ale and
                    a wonderfully relaxed drinking culture that keep bringing me back to Prague –
                    there's wit and weirdness in equal measure: a public fountain where two figures
                    pee in a puddle, spelling out literary quotations; a 1950s nuclear bunker hidden
                    beneath a city-centre hotel; and a cubist lamppost. Quirky doesn't even begin to
                    describe it. </p>
            </review>
            <highLight>
                <p> Art All Around </p>
                <p> Prague's art galleries may not have the allure of the Louvre, but Bohemian art
                    offers much to admire, from the glowing Gothic altarpieces in the Convent of St
                    Agnes, to the luscious art nouveau of Alfons Mucha, and the magnificent
                    collection of 20th-century surrealists, cubists and constructivists in the
                    Veletržní Palác. The weird and witty sculpture of David Černý punctuates
                    Prague's public spaces, and the city itself offers a smorgasbord of stunning
                    architecture, from the soaring verticals of Gothic and the exuberance of baroque
                    to the sensual elegance of art nouveau and the chiselled cheekbones of cubist
                    facades. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Where Beer is God </p>
                <p> The best beer in the world just got better. Since the invention of Pilsner
                    Urquell in 1842, the Czechs have been famous for producing some of the world's
                    finest brews. But the internationally famous brand names – Urquell, Staropramen
                    and Budvar – have been equalled, and even surpassed, by a bunch of regional
                    Czech beers and microbreweries that are catering to a renewed interest in
                    traditional brewing. Never before have Prague's pubs offered such a wide range
                    of ales – names you'll now have to get your head around include Kout na Šumavě,
                    Svijanský Rytíř and Velkopopovický Kozel. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Urban Explorations </p>
                <p> Prague's maze of cobbled lanes and hidden courtyards is a paradise for the
                    aimless wanderer, always beckoning you to explore a little further. Just a few
                    blocks away from the Old Town Square you can stumble across ancient chapels,
                    unexpected gardens, cute cafes and old-fashioned bars with hardly a tourist in
                    sight. One of the great joys of the city is its potential for exploration –
                    neighbourhoods such as Vinohrady and Bubeneč can reward the urban adventurer
                    with countless memorable cameos, from the setting sun glinting off church domes,
                    to the strains of Dvořák wafting from an open window. </p>
            </highLight>
            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Prague Castle</title>
                    <telephone>+420 224372423</telephone>
                    <address>Hradcanske namesti</address>
                    <gettingThere>Tram:22 Metro:Malostranska</gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo>www.hrad.cz</moreInfo>
                    <openHours>grounds 5am-midnight Apr-Oct, 6am-11pm Nov-Mar, gardens 10am-6pm Apr
                        &amp; Oct, to 7pm May &amp; Sep, to 9pm Jun-Aug, closed Nov-Mar, historic
                        buildings 9am-5pm Apr-Oct, to 4pm Nov-Mar </openHours>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Charles Bridge</title>
                    <address>Prague, Czech Republic</address>
                    <gettingThere>Tram: 17, 18 to Karlovy lázně, 12, 20, 22 to Malostranské
                        náměstí</gettingThere>
                    <openHours>24r</openHours>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Prague Jewishh Museum</title>
                    <telephone>+420 222 317 191</telephone>
                    <address>Reservation Centre, U starého hřbitova 3a </address>
                    <gettingThere>Metro: Staroměstská</gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo>www.jewishmuseum.cz</moreInfo>
                    <openHours>9am-6pm Sun-Fri Apr-Oct, to 4.30pm Nov-Mar</openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site14</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site6</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>
        <travelSight id="site13" rank="13" tag="Adventural; Outdoor; Arts">
            <title>Vancouver</title>
            <description>
                <p> Cool neighborhoods, drink-and-dine hot spots and spectacular vistas: all good
                    reasons why visitors fall for this lovely lotusland metropolis. \ </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s13</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="Canada"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="vancouver1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>
            <review id="r13">
                <p> By John Lee, Writer: </p>
                <p> Hummingbirds on my balcony, beaches in Stanley Park, and the annual dusting of
                    snow on surrounding mountains. Although I moved here from the UK in the 1990s, I
                    still gape at Vancouver's natural beauty. For me, it's the backdrop that sets
                    this metropolis apart. But I'm a big-city boy at heart and I've also been
                    delighted to see Vancouver grow up since I arrived. From amazing (and
                    great-value) dining to a thriving local art scene, Vancouver continues to move
                    forward – and I don't just mean the brilliant craft-beer scene (although,
                    personally, that really helps). </p>
            </review>
            <highLight>
                <p> Grassroots Arts </p>
                <p> A lack of Guggenheim-sized galleries to make its art-scene obvious means you'll
                    have to go looking for the city's cultural side, but that's its main appeal.
                    Vancouver's thriving artistic edge is local, grassroots and neighborhood-sized:
                    think of it like a locavore movement for culture lovers. Mingle with the
                    regulars at waterfront Shakespeare shows, electric dance performances, sparkling
                    theatrical events, toe-tapping live music and a huge range of public art – as
                    well as a huge open-house art crawl that enlivens East Vancouver every November.
                </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Outdoor Wonderland </p>
                <p> Those snow-dusted mountains that peek between downtown's glass towers? They're
                    less than 30 minutes away by car. Vancouverites really can ski in the morning
                    and hit the beach in the afternoon – although it's more relaxing to chill out
                    and take your time. The city's North Shore nature doorstep offers snow sports,
                    mountain biking and leisurely rainforest viewing, while the city itself is
                    studded with sandy beaches, forest trails, kayaking routes, seawall bike lanes
                    and Canada's urban green-space jewel, the mighty and highly beloved Stanley
                    Park. </p>
            </highLight>
            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Vancouver Aquarium</title>
                    <telephone>+1 6046593474</telephone>
                    <address>845 Avison Way Vancouver, Canada</address>
                    <gettingThere>Bus19</gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo>www.vanaqua.org</moreInfo>
                    <openHours>9:30am-6pm</openHours>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Stanley Park</title>
                    <address>Vancouver, Canada</address>
                    <gettingThere>Bus 19</gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo>www.vancouver.ca/parks</moreInfo>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site2</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site7</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>
        <travelSight id="site14" rank="14" tag="Food; Historical; Inspired">
            <title>Budapest</title>
            <description>
                <p> Straddling the Danube River, with the Buda Hills to the west and the Great Plain
                    to the east, Budapest is a gem of a city. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s14</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="Hungary"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="budapest1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>
            <review id="r14">
                <p> By Steve Fallon </p>
                <p> I love Budapest for all the right reasons – architecture (especially Art
                    Nouveau), romance (particularly the views from the bridges) and sticky apricot
                    jam – and some of the wrong ones, too (killer pálinka (fruit brandy), rickety
                    trolleybuses, and checking out bodies in the Turkish baths). When I first came
                    to Budapest, I was bowled over by an often sad but confident city whose history
                    seemed too complex to comprehend, by a beautiful but impenetrable language, and
                    by a people I thought I’d never know. I stayed on to learn more about all three.
                </p>
            </review>
            <highLight>
                <p> The Past at Hand </p>
                <p> They say the past is another country, but it’s always been just around the
                    corner in Budapest. Witness the bullet holes and shrapnel pockmarks on buildings
                    from WWII and the 1956 Uprising. There are sad reminders like the poignant Shoes
                    on the Danube memorial, but ones, too, of hope and reconciliation – like the
                    sword of the former secret-police building on Andrássy út now beaten into the
                    ploughshare that is the Terror House, with both sides of the story told. And
                    there’s joy as much-loved concert halls and theatres are built and renovated,
                    metro lines extended and busy streets repaved and pedestrianised. </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Eat, Drink &amp; Be Magyar </p>
                <p> There's a lot more to Hungarian food than goulash, and it remains one of the
                    most sophisticated styles of cooking in Europe. Magyars may exaggerate when they
                    say that there are three essential world cuisines: French, Chinese and their
                    own. But Budapest’s reputation as a food capital dates largely from the late
                    19th and the first half of the 20th century and, despite a fallow period under
                    communism, the city is once again commanding attention. So, too, are its
                    excellent wines – from Villány’s big-bodied reds and Somló’s flinty whites to
                    honey-gold sweet Tokaj. </p>
            </highLight>

            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Royal Palace</title>
                    <address>I Szent György tér</address>
                    <gettingThere>Bus: 16, 16A, 116</gettingThere>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Széchenyi Baths</title>
                    <address>XIV Állatkerti körút 9-11</address>
                    <gettingThere>Metro: M1 Széchenyi fürdő</gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo>www.szechenyibath.hu</moreInfo>
                    <openHours>6am-10pm</openHours>
                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Széchenyi Chain Bridge</title>
                    <address>Budapest, Hungary</address>
                    <gettingThere>Bus:16</gettingThere>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site9</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site10</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>
        <travelSight id="site15" rank="15" tag="Food; Shopping; lifestyle">
            <title>Hong Kong</title>
            <description>
                <p> This enigmatic city of skyscrapers, ancient traditions and heavenly food will
                    fascinate, whether it's your first visit or your 50th. </p>
            </description>
            <sources>
                <sourceRefId>s15</sourceRefId>
            </sources>
            <location country="China"/>
            <pictures>
                <picture path="hongkong1.jpg"/>
            </pictures>

            <review id="r15">
                <p> By Piera Chen, Writer: </p>
                <p> I love Hong Kong because it has a complexity that eludes definition, sometimes
                    even by its own people. I can be soul-searching near the Chinese border,
                    lunching with Sikhs at a Sikh temple, splurging on a set of kitchen knives,
                    arguing with bohos about the merits of a dress – all within five hours –
                    followed by a night of Cantonese opera, tango or karaoke, anywhere I choose.
                    Hong Kong is so intense and so full of possibilities that I’m glad there’s the
                    Rule of Law (and an awesome transport system) to stop it from whirling into
                    chaos. For me, that's pretty darn perfect. </p>
            </review>


            <highLight>
                <p> Culture </p>
                <p> Beyond the glass and steel of Hong Kong’s commercial persona, the city also
                    boasts a vibrant cultural scene that features the eclectic influences of its
                    Chinese roots, colonial connections and a wondrous pool of homegrown talent.
                    Here, you’re just as likely to find yourself applauding at Asia’s top film
                    festival as joining in dawn taichi or reading the couplets of a local poet to
                    the drumbeat of a dragon boat. Culture could also mean indie music under the
                    stars, a classy art walk, your first Cantonese opera – not to mention the
                    exhibitions and events staged year-round at the many museums and concert halls.
                </p>
            </highLight>
            <highLight>
                <p> Shopping </p>
                <p> From ready-to-wear Chinese jackets to bespoke kitchen knives, the sheer range
                    and variety of products on Hong Kong’s shelves is mind-bending. Every whim, need
                    and pocket is catered for in true enterprising spirit by an equally dazzling
                    number of venues – swanky malls where the moneyed shop, chic side-street
                    boutiques, antique stores, gadget bazaars, and a colourful mix of markets where
                    you can haggle to your heart’s content. The city has no sales tax so prices are
                    generally attractive to visitors. </p>
            </highLight>

            <thingsToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Victoria Peak</title>
                    <telephone>+852 25220922</telephone>
                    <address>Hong Kong China</address>
                    <gettingThere>Bus: Bus 15 from Central, below Exchange Sq Train: Peak Tram Lower
                        Terminus</gettingThere>
                    <moreInfo>www.thepeak.com.hk</moreInfo>
                    <openHours>24hr</openHours>

                </thingToDo>
                <thingToDo>
                    <title>Man Mo Temple</title>
                    <telephone>+852 25400350</telephone>
                    <address>124-126 Hollywood Rd Sheung Wan</address>
                    <gettingThere>Bus 26</gettingThere>
                    <openHours>8am-6pm</openHours>
                </thingToDo>
            </thingsToDo>
            <associations>
                <siteRefId>site9</siteRefId>
                <siteRefId>site2</siteRefId>
            </associations>
        </travelSight>

    </travelSights>
    <locations>
        <location id="l1">
            <title>CONTINENT</title>
            <location id="l2">
                <title>Asia</title>
                <location id="l3">
                    <title>Republic of Maldives</title>
                    <siteRefId>site1</siteRefId>
                </location>
                <location id="l4">
                    <title>China</title>
                    <siteRefId>site15</siteRefId>
                    <siteRefId>site5</siteRefId>
                </location>
            </location>
            <location id="l5">
                <title>Europe</title>
                <location id="l6">
                    <title>France</title>
                        <siteRefId>site2</siteRefId>
                </location>
                <location id="l8">
                    <title>Italy</title>
                        <siteRefId>site3</siteRefId>
                </location>
                <location id="l10">
                    <title>Finland</title>
                    
                        <siteRefId>site4</siteRefId>
                </location>
                <location id="l12">
                    <title>Greece</title>
                    <siteRefId>site6</siteRefId>
                </location>
                <location id="l13">
                    <title>Spain</title>
                    
                        <siteRefId>site9</siteRefId>
                </location>
                <location id="l15">
                    <title>UK</title>
                    
                        <siteRefId>site10</siteRefId>
                </location>
                <location id="l17">
                    <title>Hungary</title>
                    
                        <siteRefId>site12</siteRefId>
                </location>
            </location>
            <location id="l19">
                <title>Australia</title>
                
                    <siteRefId>site7</siteRefId>
            </location>
            <location id="l21">
                <title>North America</title>
                <location id="l22">
                    <title>Cuba</title>
                    <siteRefId>site8</siteRefId>
                </location>
                <location id="l23">
                    <title>Canada</title>
                    <siteRefId>site13</siteRefId>
                </location>
                <location id="l25">
                    <title>Maui</title>
                    <siteRefId>site11</siteRefId>
                </location>
            </location>
         
        </location>
            
        
    </locations>
    <sequence>
        <siteRefId>site1</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site5</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site4</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site9</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site10</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site15</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site2</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site3</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site11</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site12</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site6</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site7</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site8</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site13</siteRefId>
        <siteRefId>site14</siteRefId>
    </sequence>
</travelSightbase>
